// all of the quiz questions

var questions = [
    {
        Question: "The condition in an 'if/else' statement is enclosed within ______.",
        Choices: ["square brackets", "curly brackets", "parentheses"],
        Answer: "parentheses",
    },
    {
        Question: "What JavaScipt method can we use to select an html element?",
        Choices: ["document.queryselector()", "document.getElementChild", "console.log"],
        Answer: "document.queryselector()"
    },
    {
        Question: "What are the two basic groups of data types in JavaScript?",
        Choices: ["reference types and attribute", "primitive and attribute", "primitive and reference types"],
        Answer: "primitive and reference types"
    },
    {
        Question: "What html tag is NOT included in the HEAD tag?",
        Choices: ["meta", "link", "header"],
        Answer: "header"
    },
    {
        Question: "Arrays in Javascript can be used to store ______.",
        Choices: ["other arrays", "numbers & strings", "boolean", "all of the above"],
        Answer: "all of the above"
    },
    {
        Question: "String values must be enclosed within ______ when being assigned to variables.",
        Choices: ["parantheses", "quotes", "curly brackets"],
        Answer: "quotes"
    },
    {
        Question: "Commonly used data types DO NOT include:",
        Choices: ["strings", "booleans", "alerts"],
        Answer: "alerts"
    },
    {
        Question: "What attribute is used in html to decorate content?",
        Choices: ["style", "css", "src"],
        Answer: "style"
    },
    {
        Question: "A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
        Choices: ["console.log", "terminal/bash", "JavaScript"],
        Answer: "terminal/bash"
    },
    {
        Question: "Which one is NOT a looping structure in JavaScript?",
        Choices: ["for", "and", "do-while loops"],
        Answer: "and"
    }
];